Finding Aid for Paul Winston McCracken papers, 1940-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Papers, 1945-1996
  - 1983
    - World Economic Situation, World Congress of International Association of Financial Executives Institute, Jakarta, October 31, 1983 (Box 44)
    - Has Macro-Theory Failed Economic Policy? Conference of Southern Economic Association, Washington, D.C., November 20, 1983 (Box 44)
  - 1984
    - The Prosperous 1980s -- Economics Club of Detroit, February 13, 1984 (Box 44)
    - What Happened to Fiscal Policy? Compass Equitable Real Estate, fall 1984 (Box 44)
    - Book Review of: The Supply-side Revolution: An Insider's Account of Policymaking in Washington by Craig Roberts, for Journal of Economic Literature, November 28, 1984 (Box 44)
  - 1985
    - A Recession Narrowly Averted?Economic Outlook USA, First Quarter 1985 (Box 44)
    - Are Economics Laws Upside Down? Economic Club of Detroit, February 19, 1985 (Box 44)
    - The Automobile in the World Economy, U.S.-Japan Automotive Industry Conference, University of Michigan, March 5, 1985 (Box 44)
    - A Statement on the Federal Deficit from Former Chairment of the President's Council of Economic Advisers, Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, March 31, 1985 (Box 44)
    - Does Quantitative Analysis Yield Better Economic Policy? American Statistical Association, Las Vegas, August 6, 1985 (Box 44)
    - The American Economy, Pacific Forum Seminar, September 4, 1985 (Box 44)
    - Are Economic Laws Upside Down? Vital Speeches of the Day, May 1, 1985 (Box 44)
    - McCracken Sees Good Years Ahead for World Carmakers, Michigan Banking & Business News, April 1985 (Box 44)
    - Has Macro-Theory Failed Economic Policy? CFA Digest, Spring 1985 (Box 44)
    - Statement on the Gramm-Rudman Proposal. October 24, 1985 (Box 44)
  - 1986
    - Notes on the 1986 Outlook, Presented at the CEA Meeting at the White House, January 13, 1986 (Box 44)
    - International Economic Fragmentation and the World Auto Market, UMTRI Research Review, 1985 (Box 44)
    - The 1986 Economy, Economic Outlook USA, Fourth Quarter 1985 (Box 44)
    - Can the U.S. Compete? Scientific Club, February 14, 1986 (Box 44)
    - 1986 The Economy's Big Chance? Economic Club of Detroit, February 18, 1986 (Box 44)
    - The Meaning of the Budget in the American Political Process, Hillsdale College, March 9, 1986 (Box 44)
    - The U.S. International Economic Position, March 4, 1986 (Box 44)
    - The U.S. and the World Economy, Dinner Club, March 17, 1986 (Box 44)
    - The Sixth U.S.-Japan Automotive Industry Conference. April 1, 1986 (Box 44)
    - Today's Economic Climate, National Accounting and Financial Council, Los Angeles, July 2, 1986 (Box 44)
    - Reluctance to Prosper, Paper delivered to the National Association of Business Economist, September 18, 1986 (Box 44)
    - Introduction to Dr. Paul W. McCracken by Don R. Conlan, at the NABE Annual Meeting, Boston, September 18, 1986 (Box 44)
    - Trade, Taxes & the 1987 Economy, Paper presented to the Economic Club of Phoenix, October 22, 1986 (Box 44)
  - 1987
    - Trade Will Improve, January 17, 1987 (Box 44)
    - An Era of Non-Euclidean Economics? Sixteenth Annual Economic Seminar, Florida, January 19, 1987 (Box 44)
    - Ruminations of an Ex-Economist, Conference of Business Economists, Washington, D.C., February 12, 1987 (Box 44)
    - The Meaning of the Budget in the American Political Process, IMPRIMIS, Hillsdale College, February 1987 (Box 44)
    - Can Economic Policy Manage the Economy? Engle Lecture, American College, Bryn Mawr, Pennsylvania, May 6, 1987 (Box 44)
    - William Penn Commencement, William Penn College May 10, 1987 (Box 44)
    - Liberal Economies: A "Reluctance to Prosper." Economic Impact, No. 59 A Quarterly Review of World Economics, 1987 (Box 44)
    - Can the U.S. Survive a Globalized Economy? Iowa Bankers Association, September 21, 1987 (Box 44)
    - Marvin Bower Award, Joint Council on Economic Education, December 4, 1987 (Box 44)
  - 1988
    - The Problem of "Other People's Habits," Japan Society, New York, February 25, 1988 (Box 44)
    - Remarks at Texas Instruments Dinner, March 7, 1988 (Box 44)
    - Is America Becoming More Competitive? Japan Society of Northern California, San Francisco, March 16, 1988 (Box 44)
    - The Globalization of Economic Life, Hallmarks of Successful International Business Programs, Council on International Educational Exchange, August 1988 (Box 44)
    - The University and Education for Business. Rackham 50th Symposium, University of Michigan, October 18, 1988 (Box 44)
  - 1989
    - The Channel Narrows, Economic Outlook, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Economic Policy Coordination, Dewey Daane Conference, April 13-14, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Remarks to Michigan State Chamber of Commerce, July 27, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Remarks, August 9, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Introductory Remarks, Herb Stein Seidman Award, September 18, 1989 (Box 44)
    - Introduction of Dr. James J. Duderstadt, September 19, 1989 (Box 44)
  - 1990
    - Random Thoughts on Transition Economics, Paper presented at the Hudson Institute to the Blue Ribbon Commission drawing up plans for Hungary's Economic Transition, January 8, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Needed: An International Strategy, Address to the Economic Club of Detroit, March 19, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Remarks, National Launching, Forward in Faith Campaign of William Penn College, May 5, 1990 (Box 44)
    - East Asian Development and U.S. Financial Issues in the 1990s Conference on East Asia and Global Challenge, October 18, 1990 (Box 44)
  - 1991
    - A Great Time to be Alive Economically Speaking, March 20, 1991 (Box 44)
    - Luncheon address to the CEO Associates for Progress, Kalamazoo, July 18, 1991 (Box 44)
    - Opening Remarks: The Automobile..., Automotive Management Briefing, Traverse City, August 7, 1991 (Box 44)
    - The Victory of the Liberal Order? IMDF, October 21, 1991 (Box 44)
  - 1992
    - D. Maynard Phelps Eulogy, January 9, 1993 (Box 44)
    - Economic Policy Making in the 1990s Davidson College, March 25, 1993 (Box 44)
    - Should the Employment Act of 1946 Be Repealed? Kentucky Economic Association, September 17, 1993 (Box 44)
    - N.A.F.T.A. and Unemployment Detroit Free Press, November 1993 (Box 44)
  - 1994
    - The Economy-1994 Florida Council for 100, January 24, 1994 (Box 44)
    - 1994s Urgent Agenda: More Vigorous Economic Growth. Address to the Economic Club of Detroit, February 7, 1994 (Box 44)
    - The G-7 Comes to Town, Detroit Free Press, February 15, 1994 (Box 44)
    - Interview with Dr. Paul McCracken by Yanek Mieczkowski, February 1996 (Box 44)
    - Remarks on International Economic Policy, November 9, 1994 (Box 44)
    - A Zero Inflation Mandate? (Box 44)
  - 1995
    - Remarks, CEA Reception, January 7, 1995 (Box 44)
  - 1996
    - Economic Policy in the Nixon Years, Presidential Studies Quarterly, Winter 1996 (Box 44)
- Papers, 1937-2002
  - 1937-1938
    - The Pedagogy of Mathematics, January 14, 1937 (Box 46)
    - The Berea Reading Problem, June 24, 1938 (Box 46)
    - An Outline of Procedure for the Formulation of a Guidance Program in the Foundation School, June 28, 1939 (Box 46)
  - 1940-1949
    - The Safety-Fund System of New York, 1940 (Box 46)
    - Consumer Durables and Business Cycles, January 14, 1942 (Box 46)
    - Thesis -- Cyclical Implications of Wartime Liquid Asset Accumulation, April 1, 1948 (Box 46)
    - Business Cycles by Schumpeter, 1948, 2 volumes (Box 46)
  - 1950-1959
    - An Analysis of Some Factors Associated with Variability in Rates of Return on Permanent Investment of Large American Business, August 18, 1950 (Box 46)
    - Markets After the Defense Expansion, 1952 (Box 46)
    - The Current Business Situation, January-May 1958 (Box 46)
    - Implications of Recent Economic Developments for Policy, February 12, 1958 (Box 46)
    - Business Conditions Improved, July 17, 1958 (Box 46)
  - 1960-1969
    - Economic Suggestions, January 17, 1961 (Box 47)
    - Observations on India's Strategy of Economic Policy, December 1963 (Box 47)
    - Economic Progress and the Utility Industry, 1964 (Box 47)
    - Prospects for 1965 The Rising Business Trend Continues, December 1964 (Box 47)
    - Business Strategy for an Uncertain Future, December 7, 1964 (Box 47)
    - Notes on Business Conditions, 1964-1966 (Box 47)
    - 1965 A Year of Gains and Problems, 1965 (Box 47)
    - The Political Position of the Council of Economic Advisers, January 19, 1966 (Box 47)
    - The 21st Century, This University, and Dog-Legs, March 15, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Can Full Employment be Sustained?, August 1966 (Box 47)
    - An Elder Statesman Looks at the New Economics, July 1967 (Box 47)
    - Economic Policy on the Spot, June 29, 1968 (Box 47)
    - Beyond 1969 January 1969 (Box 47)
  - 1970-1973
    - Economic Priorities in the 1970s, 1970 (Box 47)
    - Report to the National Commission on Productivity by the Council of Economic Advisors, 1970-1980, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - The Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 47)
      (2 volumes, signed by President Nixon)
    - 1972 Annual Business Conference, 1972 (Box 47)
    - Will the New Economic Expansion Endure, November 13, 1972 (Box 47)
    - The Changing Character of Japan-U.S. Economic Relationships, December 1973 (Box 47)
  - 1974
    - Economic Part of Power Study, 1974 (Box 47)
    - Opening Remarks to the Conference Board on U.S.-Japan Economic Policy, April 1, 1974 (Box 47)
    - The Problems of Adjustment in the U.S. Economy, May 2, 1974 (Box 47)
    - Competition and Market Concentration in the American Economy, June 1974 (Box 47)
  - 1975
    - Exhortation and Controls: The Search for a Wage-Pride Policy 1945-1971, 1975 (Box 47)
    - Financing the Future, 1975 (Box 47)
    - The 1976 U.S. Economic Outlook, 1975 (Box 47)
    - The Hazards of '76, 1975 (Box 47)
    - Stabilization is Home Grown?, August 5, 1975 (Box 47)
    - Summary Remarks to American Association of Equipment Lessors, October 27, 1975 (Box 47)
    - Economic Shadows and Substance for 1976 November3, 1975 (Box 47)
  - 1976
    - Forecast of U.S. Economy for 1977, 1976 (Box 47)
    - Remarks at 75-76 Tsai Forum, January 8, 1976 (Box 47)
    - Reflections on Economic Advising, March 1976 (Box 47)
    - On a Strategy for the Future, April 30, 1976 (Box 47)
    - Remarks to the American Mining Congress, September 27, 1976 (Box 47)
    - The Investment Problem, November 12, 1976 (Box 47)
  - 1977
    - The Accelerating Expansion of 1977, 1977 (Box 47)
    - Statement to Meeting of the OECD Council, June 24, 1977 (Box 47)
    - Remarks to the 4th Canadian Financial Conference, June 28, 1977 (Box 47)
    - Why We've Got to Clamp Down on Government Spending, July 1977 (Box 47)
    - Government and Economic Progress, September 1977 (Box 47)
  - 1978-1979
    - Towards Full Employment and Price Stability, 1978 (Box 47)
    - The Economic Agenda for 1978 January 19, 78 (Box 47)
    - We Can Have Low Rates of Inflation and Unemployment, 1979 (Box 47)
    - 1979 A Prologue to What?, February 5, 1979 (Box 47)
  - 1980-1989
    - Is There a Future for the Class of 1982?, May 1, 1982 (Box 47)
    - On the Proposal for an Industrial Policy, 1984 (Box 47)
    - The World Economy Bounces Back, August 1, 1984 (Box 47)
    - The Bishop's Letter on the Economy, January 1985 (Box 47)
    - 1989 -- A Year to be Alert, 1989 (Box 47)
    - Introductory Remarks to Seidman Award, September 15, 1989 (Box 47)
  - 1990-1999
    - Random Thoughts on Transition Economics, January 8, 1990 (Box 47)
    - East Asian Development and U.S. Financial Issues in the 1990s, October 18, 1990 (Box 47)
    - A Great Time to be Alive Economically Speaking, March 20, 1991 (Box 47)
    - The Victory of the Liberal Order?, October 21, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Disestablishmentarianization and Democracy, April 1992 (Box 47)
    - China-Economic Notes, 1995 (Box 47)
    - Becoming an Economic Policy Adviser, 1999 (Box 47)
  - 2002
    - Nixon Book Project, April 2002 (Box 47)
  - Undated
    - Beginning a Long Expansion (Box 47)
    - By God (Box 47)
    - Coffin Family History (Box 47)
    - Economic Policy History Biography (Box 47)
    - Economic Policy in the Nixon Years (Box 47)
    - Energy and the Market (Box 47)
    - Is Rent Cost? (Box 47)
    - It Was God (Box 47)
    - The Problems of Prosperity (Box 47)
    - Should the Employment Act of 1946 Be Repealed? (Box 47)
    - Statement on S.740 (Box 47)
    - Steel Prices, Volume and Costs (Box 47)
    - Theory of Public Expenditures (Box 47)
    - Wage and Price Control (Box 47)
    - WSJ (Box 47)
    - Untitled Papers (Box 47)
- University Lecture Notes
  The University Lectures Notes series contains notes McCracken took in his time as a student, and notes and course material from his time as a professor. Most courses are labeled by the designated class number, though some are organized by class title. Three notebooks have no label of what they are for.
  - Economics 101 (Box 48)
  - Economics 103a, 113b (Box 48)
  - Economics 121a (Box 48)
  - Economics 121b (Box 48)
  - Economics 141 (Box 48)
  - Economics 521a, 545 (Box 48)
  - Economics 611 (Box 48)
  - Economic History (Box 48)
  - Economic Theory (Box 48)
  - Graduate School of Banking (Box 48)
  - Macro-Economic Phenomena (Box 48)
  - Notebooks, 4 folders (Box 48)
  - Proseminar in Business Economics B.E. 801, 1975 (Box 48)
  - Surveys (Box 48)
  - Unlabeled Notebooks, 3 folders (Box 48)
- Wall Street Journal Articles
  The Wall Street Journal series is made up of the complete collection of articles that McCracken submitted and had published in the Wall Street Journal between 1972 and 1995. Most files contain a printout of the article as well as the newspaper clipping of the article. They are organized in reverse chronological order.
  - Deficits and the Economy, April 13, 1995 (Box 49)
  - We Can Still Balance the Budget, March 6, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Time for an Economic Summit, September 28, 1994 (Box 49)
  - Toward an Illiberal Trading System, April 1994 (Box 49)
  - Unemployment -- The Crisis Continues, January 7, 1994 (Box 49)
  - Getting the Direction Right, December 1993 (Box 49)
  - Better Times Ahead, July 21, 1993 (Box 49)
  - The Post-Stimulus Challenge, April 28, 1993 (Box 49)
  - It's the Economy Stupid, January 1993 (Box 49)
  - Make No Little Plans..., November 1992 (Box 49)
  - The Myth of 'Chronic' Unemployment, September 16, 1992 (Box 49)
  - Why Things Aren't Getting Better, July 23, 1992 (Box 49)
  - The Best Recession Policy: Investment, January 17, 1992 (Box 49)
  - The Big Domestic Issue: Slow Growth, October 4, 1991 (Box 49)
  - The Fed's Not-So-Bad Monetary Policy, July 18, 1991 (Box 49)
  - The Anxieties of 1990, December 5, 1990 (Box 49)
  - Gasoline Prices are Much Too Low, October 10, 1990 (Box 49)
  - The Big Budget Job, May 29, 1990 (Box 49)
  - Social Scrutiny: Just Another Handout, February 5, 1990 (Box 49)
  - Maybe You Can't Get There From Here, July 24, 1989 (Box 49)
  - Why U.S. Exports Are a Casualty, March 3, 1989 (Box 49)
  - Lick the American Disease Before It's an Epidemic, January 16, 1989 (Box 49)
  - Bush, the Budget and the Narrow Path, December 6, 1988 (Box 49)
  - No Times for Vagueness on Budget Policy, May 18, 1988 (Box 49)
  - Some Economic Cliff Notes, December 23, 1987 (Box 49)
  - Governance and the Gridlock, September 2, 1987 (Box 49)
  - The Rust Belt's Coming Revival, March 30, 1987 (Box 49)
  - Toward World Economic Disintegration, February 9, 1987 (Box 49)
  - Tokyo Summit: More Than Good Theater, May 23, 1986 (Box 49)
  - The Fiscal Picture Improves, but..., March 17, 1986 (Box 49)
  - Sharpen U.S. Competitive Skills, December 20, 1985 (Box 49)
  - Tackling the Tokyo Trade Imbalance, September 16, 1985 (Box 49)
  - Eurosclerosis Eats at U.S. Exports, July 9, 1985 (Box 49)
  - The Summit as a Listening Post, May 1, 1985 (Box 49)
  - Light at the End of the Budget Tunnel, March 19, 1985 (Box 49)
  - The Year of the Budget, December 19, 1984 (Box 49)
  - The World Economy Bounces Back, August 1, 1984 (Box 49)
  - On the Inflation Watch, April 11, 1984 (Box 49)
  - Gobbling Up the Economic Pie, February 28, 1984 (Box 49)
  - Reaganomics is Ready for Stage Two, January 19, 1984 (Box 49)
  - The Deficit Crisis That Won't Go Away, August 26, 1983 (Box 49)
  - A Consensus to Live Within Our Means?, June 28, 1983 (Box 49)
  - Helping Along the Economic Recovery, March 7, 1983 (Box 49)
  - Tough Times for Economic Policy Makers, January 3, 1983 (Box 49)
  - Congress Gets a Joshua Complex, September 24, 1982 (Box 49)
  - The International Economic Agenda, June 25, 1982 (Box 49)
  - The Budget: Times for Action is Short, April 14, 1982 (Box 49)
  - Economic Systems and Security, February 17, 1982 (Box 49)
  - Why Are We Having Another Recession?, December 31, 1981 (Box 49)
  - The Risk of Making Policies in a Stampede, October 22, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Economic Policy in the U.S.: Chapter Two, August 27, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Reagan's Tax Plan Makes Sense, June 10, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Japanese-U.S. Trade: The Larger Problem, April 23, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Reagan's Budget: A Fundamental Change?, March 4, 1981 (Box 49)
  - A United States 'Industrial Policy', January 12, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Auguries for Economic Policy, November 13, 1980 (Box 49)
  - The Road to Budget Balance, August 18, 1980 (Box 49)
  - The Fading American Importance, June 17, 1980 (Box 49)
  - The Current Economic Strategy, May 9, 1980 (Box 49)
  - Congress and the Budget Beanstalk, February 29, 1980 (Box 49)
  - National Defense is Affordable, January 28, 1980 (Box 49)
  - Revitalization in the 1980s, December 20, 1979 (Box 49)
  - After the Coming Recession, October 17, 1979 (Box 49)
  - External Disciplines on Policy, September 17, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Carter's Confidence Speech, August 1, 1979 (Box 49)
  - The 'Rolling Readjustment' Scenario, July 3, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Energy and the Importance of Power, May 23, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Our Unmysterious Inflation, April 23, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Slaying the Inflation Dragon, March 29, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Iran: Ill Wind Blowing Good?, February 26, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Getting Tough with Inflation, December 15, 1978 (Box 49)
  - Is the U.S. Now in Step, November 20, 1978 (Box 49)
  - Building on Good Economic News, October 19, 1978 (Box 49)
  - The Cosmetic War on Inflation, August 18, 1978 (Box 49)
  - The Opportunity in Bonn, July 14, 1978 (Box 49)
  - Floating Rates and World Trade, June 2, 1978 (Box 49)
  - Resist Fiscal Sin -- Now, April 26, 1978 (Box 49)
  - Inflation Must Be Fought, March 13, 1978 (Box 49)
  - The Dollar and Economic Growth, January 26, 1978 (Box 49)
  - The President and the Fed, December 16, 1977 (Box 49)
  - Fragile Economic Progress, November 2, 1977 (Box 49)
  - The Indistinct Bugle, August 29, 1977 (Box 49)
  - Reducing the Inflation Rate, July 25, 1977 (Box 49)
  - The Demagoguery Over Energy, May 16, 1977 (Box 49)
  - Fiscal Stimulus and Inflation, March 24, 1977 (Box 49)
  - The New Team's Economic Policy, January 17, 1977 (Box 49)
  - The New Mood on Public Spending, October 29, 1976 (Box 49)
  - A Dangerous Investment Gap, September 17, 1976 (Box 49)
  - The Puerto Rico Agenda, June 23, 1976 (Box 49)
  - The Crucial Year Ahead, May 3, 1976 (Box 49)
  - Public Policy and the Economy, March 22, 1976 (Box 49)
  - The Future of the U.S.-Soviet Trade, February 23, 1976 (Box 49)
  - The Budget and the Economy, January 8, 1976 (Box 49)
  - The Targets for Economic Policy, November 25, 1975 (Box 49)
  - New York City and the Economy, October 17, 1975 (Box 49)
  - A Way Out of the World's Slump, September 17, 1975 (Box 49)
  - Monetary Policy and the Congress, July 10, 1975 (Box 49)
  - A Long Expansion Ahead, June 11, 1975 (Box 49)
  - 1974's Economic Air Pocket, April 25, 1975 (Box 49)
  - Beleaguered Days for the Fed, March 21, 1975 (Box 49)
  - Mixing Fiscal and Monetary Policies, February 21, 1975 (Box 49)
  - Energy Policy's Staying Power, December 26, 1974 (Box 49)
  - The Complex Route to Stability, November 20, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Bicentennial Stability, October 23, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Let's Read the Minutes, August 29, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Are the 'Latter Days' Upon Us?, July 22, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Catching the Inflation Rabbit, May 29, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Is It Time for Less Restraint?, April 17, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Should Controls Be Extended?, March 20, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Can Fiscal Policy be Managed? (Box 49)
  - 1974's Basic Problem -- Inflation, February 21, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Energy and 1974 Business Conditions, December 20, 1973 (Box 49)
  - Coupon Book Economics, November 26, 1973 (Box 49)
  - The Need for More Plant Capacity, October 17, 1973 (Box 49)
  - America's Expanding Foreign Trade, September 20, 1973 (Box 49)
  - Two Years and Four Phases Later, August 23, 1973 (Box 49)
  - Controls, Inevitable -- and Perilous, June 29, 1973 (Box 49)
  - Elevating the Transatlantic Dialog, May 24, 1973 (Box 49)
  - The Economy: Just Short of Boiling, April 27, 1973 (Box 49)
  - The Case of Flexibility in Phase 3, March 6, 1973 (Box 49)
  - Has Phase 3 Fooled Everybody?, January 23, 1973 (Box 49)
  - Extending Controls: A Lesser Risk, December 21, 1972 (Box 49)
  - How Soon to Brake the Economy?, November 22, 1972 (Box 49)
  - Congress Can Regain Fiscal Control, October 20, 1972 (Box 49)
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Materials series is arranged alphabetically. It is comprised of photographs and moving images on videocassettes. Photographs of note include White House Official Photographs of a Council of Economic Advisors sessions at Camp David and in the Oval Office. Individuals featured include McCracken, Richard Nixon, George H. Bush, Sam Sturgis, and Alan Greenspan. Additional photographs which had been framed are organized chronologically. Another grouping includes signed photographs and groups, identified and unidentified and two signed political cartoons
  - Photographs
    - 1950s (Box 49)
    - 1961 (Box 49)
    - 1968 (Box 49)
    - 1969 (Box 49)
    - 1973 (Box 49)
    - 1975 (Box 49)
    - 1977 (Box 49)
    - 1978 (Box 49)
    - 1979 (Box 49)
    - 1980 (Box 49)
    - 1981 (Box 49)
    - 1982 (Box 49)
    - 1983 (Box 49)
    - 1984 (Box 49)
    - 1985 (Box 49)
    - 1986 (Box 49)
    - 1987 (Box 49)
    - 1988 (Box 49)
    - 1989 (Box 49)
    - 1990 (Box 49)
    - 1991 (Box 49)
    - 1992 (Box 49)
    - 1994 (Box 49)
    - 2010 (Box 49)
    - Unidentified Years (Box 49)
    - Signed Photographs (Box 51)
      - Warren E. Burger (Box 51)
      - John D. Ehrlichman (Box 51)
      - Gerald R. Ford (Box 51)
      - Hendrik "Hank" Houthakker (Box 51)
      - Robert Mayo (Box 51)
      - Richard Nixon, 1969 (Box 51)
      - Unidentified (Box 51)
      - Unidentified (Box 51)
      - Former Chairmen of the Council of Economic Advisors, 1994 (Box 51)
      - White House Staff ? (Box 51)
    - Political Cartoons
      - Hugh Haynie, "As a last resort (perish the thought!) I May have to grab the reins,"Courier-Journal, 1971 (Box 51)
      - Lee Lorenz "You can come out now, Mr. Plenum. The inflation alert is over," New Yorker January 30, 1971 (Box 51)
    - Photographs with Presidents (Box 52)
    - Groups-Identified Photographs (Box 52)
    - Unidentified Groups (Box 52)
    - Council of Economic Advisors, 1970-1971 (Box 26)
    - Friends and Colleagues (Box 26)
    - Groups (American Association of Neurological Surgeons) (Box 26)
    - Groups (Business Outlook Forum, Honolulu) (Box 26)
    - Groups (Identified) (Box 26)
    - Groups (Unidentified) (Box 26)
    - McCracken in the Classroom, undated (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26)
    - Pepperdine University, April 19, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Portraits (Box 26)
    - United States-Japan Meeting on the Auto Study, April 3, 1981 (Box 26)
    - University of Michigan Business School Faculty and Wives, undated (Box 26)
  - Videocassettes